<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CryptoNews</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">News</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Learn</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello</string>
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>
    <string name="theme">Themes</string>
    <string name="light_theme">Light</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="menu_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_prognoses">"Forecasts "</string>
    <string name="curse_change">Exchange rate change in % for:</string>
    <string name="market_stat">Brief market statistics</string>
    <string name="sort">Sorting:</string>
    <string name="list_settings">List settings</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="source_code">Source code</string>
    <string name="market_stats">Market statistics:</string>
    <string name="price">Price:</string>
    <string name="total_supply">"Gen. offer "</string>
    <string name="max_supply">Max. offer</string>
    <string name="market_cap_full">Market cap.</string>
    <string name="market_cap_small">MC</string>
    <string name="main">Main</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="perc_1h">% for 1h.</string>
    <string name="perc_1d">% for 1d.</string>
    <string name="perc_7d">% for 7d.</string>
    <string name="rang">Rang</string>
    <string name="price_dialog">Price</string>
    <string name="h1">1h.</string>
    <string name="d1">1d.</string>
    <string name="d7">7d.</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="altcoin_title">Altcoin</string>
    <string name="bitcoin_title">Bitcoin</string>
    <string name="blockchain_title">Blockchain</string>
    <string name="bulls_title">Bulls</string>
    <string name="flats_title">Flat</string>
    <string name="gap_title">Gap</string>
    <string name="dump_title">Dump</string>
    <string name="green_title">Green candle</string>
    <string name="inside_title">Inside</string>
    <string name="cryptowallet_title">Cryptocurrency</string>
    <string name="kits_title">Whales</string>
    <string name="red_title">Red candle</string>
    <string name="bears_title">Bears</string>
    <string name="otskok_title">Rebound</string>
    <string name="pump_title">Pump</string>
    <string name="hand_title">Shoulder</string>
    <string name="sliv_title">Drain</string>
    <string name="toTheMoon_title">To the Moon</string>
    <string name="shitcoin_title">Shitcoin</string>
    <string name="shitcoin">"unattractive cryptocurrency for investment. "</string>
    <string name="toTheMoon">"a sharp increase in the rate of cryptocurrencies (“flight to the moon”). "</string>
    <string name="sliv">"mass sale of cryptocurrencies. "</string>
    <string name="hand">"a loan that a broker can provide to a client to purchase securities backed by assets held in the client's account. Although credit can be provided not only in cash, but also in the form of securities, this term is usually used to refer to long positions opened on credit. Shoulder width is measured in relation to the size of the client account. For example: leverage of 2 to 1 means the possibility of obtaining 2 dollars of credit for 1 dollar of existing assets. "</string>
    <string name="pump">"mass purchase of cryptocurrency, aimed at artificial appreciation. "</string>
    <string name="otskok">"a phenomenon that usually occurs when a stock price falls (grows) sharply, when the price reaches a strong support (resistance) level, leads to an increase in buying (selling). As a result, the fall (growth) is temporarily suspended and the price rises (falls) somewhat from the levels reached, as if bouncing off like a ball. Then the movement of quotes resumes in the direction preceding the rebound. If such a continuation of the movement does not occur, then the rebound turns into a reversal. Unlike bounce, the term \"dead cat jump\" only refers to the situation where the bounce occurs during cushioning. "</string>
    <string name="bears">"these are traders who play on the downside of the price and deliberately reduce it to a minimum. "</string>
    <string name="red">"a sharp drop in the cryptocurrency rate, indicated in red on the chart. "</string>
    <string name="kits">"these are key exchange players who own a large amount of cryptocurrency and influence the market. "</string>
    <string name="cryptowallet">"this is a kind of digital currency, accounting for internal units of account of which is provided by a decentralized payment system operating in a fully automatic mode. "</string>
    <string name="inside">"important information that can affect stock quotes, but is available at the time of its appearance only to a narrow circle of people - insiders. Insiders use this information to their advantage until it becomes available to other participants. "</string>
    <string name="green">"the rapid growth of the cryptocurrency rate, marked in green on the chart. "</string>
    <string name="dump">"intentionally selling cryptocurrencies in gigantic quantities to artificially depreciate "</string>
    <string name="gap">"a significant gap, a jump in quotes. Usually happens between the price of the morning open and the previous evening close of the market. Occurs in the event of a change in the market situation during the time until the auction was held. "</string>
    <string name="flats">"Unlike a trend, a sideways movement characterizes the movement of the market without a clearly defined direction. Quotes move as if sideways, flat - smooth (eng.). However, a really even sidewall is quite rare. "</string>
    <string name="bulls">traders playing on the increase in the prices of crypto-currencies</string>
    <string name="blockchain">"a decentralized database that is simultaneously stored on many computers connected to each other on the Internet. The word \"blockchain\" is translated from English as \"chain of blocks\". "</string>
    <string name="bitcoin">"the name of the first cryptocurrency. "</string>
    <string name="altcoin">"it is any cryptocurrency launched after bitcoin. Simply put, altcoins, of which there are already hundreds of varieties, act as improved alternatives to bitcoin. "</string>
</resources>